>> Brian Holt: 我们继续进行迁移。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's go ahead and
start migrating things.
因此，缺省情况下， TypeScript 不会检查名为 .js的文件。
So by default, TypeScript will not
check files that are called .js.
这对我们是有帮助的因为我们可以在一个半迁徙的
This is kinda helpful for us, because we
can leave our project in a semi-migrated
状态，我们可以用一块来把它移动，不要弄坏它的应用。
state, and we could just migrate it piece
by piece and not break the application.
我们什么都不用做
We don't have to do
everything all at once.
我们就从一个小件开始就开始了
So we're just gonna start with
just like one small piece.
所以我们先从莫达 .js 开始吧，对吧 ?
So let's go ahead and
start with the Modal.js right here, right?
所以我要你右键单击这个
So I want you to right-click on this,
并表示重命名 Modal.tsx。
and say rename Modal.tsx.
我知道我们没有为这件事做 jsx 的事对吧
Now I know we didn't do jsx for
the JS parts of this, right?
但对于 TypeScript ，它需要更多或更少的时间。
But with TypeScript,
it's more or less required.
你可以得到它但别担心
You can get around it, but
let's just not worry about it.
我们还是用点吧
Let's just stick with .tsx, okay?
然后突然之间一切都开始变成红色
And then all of a sudden, everything's
going to start turning red and
对你大喊大叫对吧
yelling at you, right?
Cuz TypeScript 是愤怒的。
Cuz TypeScript is angry.
>> Brian Holt: 对不起。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Sorry.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，编译器对我们感到愤怒。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
the compiler is angry at us.
所以现在我们要经历
So now we have to go through and
识别出不知道怎么想的东西
identify things that it doesn't
know how to figure out.
我们得给它更多的提示，对吗 ?
We have to give it more hints, right?
所以在一些事情上，它能把它弄明白，对吧 ?
So on some things,
it can just figure it out, right?
可以看到莫达根在这里说我知道这是 HTMLElement
It can see modalRoot right here and say,
like, I know this is an HTMLElement or
因为我知道 document.getElementById 是什么。
null because I know what
document.getElementById does.
但我不知道孩子是什么，对我来说是新的。
But I don't know what the hell
children is, that's new to me.
所以，让我们继续做一些这些事情。
So let's go ahead and
start doing some of these things.
>> Brian Holt: So Modal 此处， >> Brian Holt: 这是一个 React。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So Modal here,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is a React.
>> Brian Holt: 函数组件，函数组件，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Function component,
function component,
功能组件，在其中。
function component, there it is.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我告诉它这是一个功能组件，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So, I told it that
this is a function component,
它是从这里自动为我进口的
which it imported from React
here automatically for me.
现在它知道莫达尔是个 FunctionComponent
And so now it knows Modal's
a FunctionComponent, which means it knows
因为它知道 FunctionComponent 是什么，是吗 ?
what children is now because it knows
what FunctionComponent is, right?
只要在适当的地方告诉它正确的提示它就可以
So just by telling it the right hints
in the right places, it's able to like,
好吧我知道这些点是怎么连接的对吧
okay, I see how these dots connect, right?
它会试图让你尽可能地为它做最起码的工作。
And it's going to try to get you to
do the bare minimum possible for it.
但如果我现在悬浮在这里，我注意到 React 子代是 React.ReactNode。
But if I hover over this now, I notice
that React children is React.ReactNode.
所以我不需要告诉它，因为它知道。
So I don't have to tell it that,
because it knows.
> > Brian Holt: 那么现在它会很愤怒，因为它会说，嘿，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now it's gonna be angry
at this, because it's gonna say, hey,
elRef 是这样不好的
elRef is, like this isn't good.
所以我们可以在这里做一些事情。
So we can do a couple of things here.
首先，我们已经知道 React.Modal 不会经常重新呈现。
The first thing, we already know that
React.Modal doesn't re-render very often.
所以我们可以直接把它放在这里。
So we can actually just
put this directly in here.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 现在这样会好起来的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
now that's gonna be okay.
库兹这一切都是个基本的问题对吧
Cuz this is always gonna
be a div basically, right?
>> Brian Holt: 好的，在这里使用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, useEffect here.
所以我们要说的第一件事是没有莫达根
So the first thing we're gonna say
here is if there's no modalRoot.
>> Brian Holt: 将始终存在，但返回。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Which there always will be,
but return.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
that's gonna do away with this part.
对，因为现在它知道
Right, because now, it knows for
如果不存在莫达根我就不能来了对吧
a fact that I can't get here
unless modalRoot exists, right?
这就是我告诉你的
And this is what I'm telling you,
它不会让你做 X2 大写的，对吧 ?
that it won't let you do things
like X2 uppercase, right?
像模态根一样
Like modal root.
如果不存在，那么模态根将为空，对吗 ?
If this doesn't exist,
then modal root is gonna be null, right?
然后这会导致错误，而 TypeScript不太酷。
And then this would cause an error and
TypeScript's not cool with that.
所以一旦你做到了，你就需要在这里做一件事
So once you've done that, then the next
thing that you need to do here is you need
把它变成一个功能
to make this into a function.
因为它不指望能从这个功能中得到任何东西
Because it doesn't expect anything
to get back from this function,
它预期这是一个虚空回归，并且
it expects that this is a void return, and
这在技术上是有回报的
this is technically something
that returns something.
只要我们能这么做
So as long as we make this so
再也回不来了，就又开心了，对吧 ?
it doesn't return anything anymore,
then it's happy again, right?
但是该函数的调用签名需要返回任何内容。
But the call signature of this
function needs to be return nothing.
就在 14 号线上
Right there on line 14.